{"quizName":"quiz_2","questions":{"An AlphaAnimation could be used on a View to do what?":{"question":"An AlphaAnimation could be used on a View to do what?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Rotate the View."},{"key":"B.","value":"Move the View across the screen."},{"key":"C.","value":"Make the View become larger or smaller."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these."}]},"Which of the following types of animations are not supported by the Android package android.view.animation?":{"question":"Which of the following types of animations are not supported by the Android package android.view.animation?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Scaling"},{"key":"B.","value":"Rotation"},{"key":"C.","value":"All these are supported."},{"key":"D.","value":"Alpha"}]},"The ___ can be sued to determine if the device is facing north, south, east, or west.":{"question":"The ___ can be sued to determine if the device is facing north, south, east, or west.","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"pitch"},{"key":"B.","value":"yaw"},{"key":"C.","value":"roll"}]},"What sensor is ideal for accurately detecting rotations about three axis without being affected by external forces like gravity?":{"question":"What sensor is ideal for accurately detecting rotations about three axis without being affected by external forces like gravity?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"pedometer"},{"key":"B.","value":"accelerometer"},{"key":"C.","value":"magnetometer"},{"key":"D.","value":"gyroscope"}]},"_____ is established as the preferred format for an image file in Android.":{"question":"_____ is established as the preferred format for an image file in Android.","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"GIF"},{"key":"B.","value":"PNG"},{"key":"C.","value":"JPG"}]},"Why would a Drawable's setBounds() method be called?":{"question":"Why would a Drawable's setBounds() method be called?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"To specify the boundaries of the View containing the Drawable."},{"key":"B.","value":"To specify the animation used on the boundaries of the Drawable."},{"key":"C.","value":"To set properties like color or alpha on the Drawable."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these."}]},"What type of rotation motion is used to determine if an Android device is facing north, south, east, or west?":{"question":"What type of rotation motion is used to determine if an Android device is facing north, south, east, or west?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"yaw"},{"key":"B.","value":"roll"},{"key":"C.","value":"pitch"},{"key":"D.","value":"axis"}]},"A programmer would implement the ___________ interface to create a separate thread.":{"question":"A programmer would implement the ___________ interface to create a separate thread.","answer":"Runnable","score":"2","options":"input"},"The android:duration attribute of an &lt;item&gt; from an XML &lt;animation-list&gt; is used to specify what?":{"question":"The android:duration attribute of an &lt;item&gt; from an XML &lt;animation-list&gt; is used to specify what?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"How long the entire animation sequence should last."},{"key":"B.","value":"How long the item should be displayed."},{"key":"C.","value":"How long the item should be hidden."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these."}]},"Shape attributes can be applied using tags, such as ___:":{"question":"Shape attributes can be applied using tags, such as ___:","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"&lt;gradient&gt;"},{"key":"B.","value":"&lt;padding&gt;"},{"key":"C.","value":"&lt;corners&gt;"},{"key":"D.","value":"all of these."}]},"Which of these touch gestures is typically associated with zooming?":{"question":"Which of these touch gestures is typically associated with zooming?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Scroll"},{"key":"B.","value":"Long press"},{"key":"C.","value":"Double tap"},{"key":"D.","value":"Fling"}]},"Which of the following AsyncTask methods is not invoked on the UI thread?":{"question":"Which of the following AsyncTask methods is not invoked on the UI thread?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onPreExecute() and doInBackground()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onProgressUpdate()"},{"key":"C.","value":"doInBackground()"},{"key":"D.","value":"onPreExecute()"}]},"For every touch gesture, a set of details are provided as identification of the gesture. They include ____ .":{"question":"For every touch gesture, a set of details are provided as identification of the gesture. They include ____ .","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Location of the touch(s)."},{"key":"B.","value":"Amount of pressure applied by the touch."},{"key":"C.","value":"Size of the finger touch."},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these."}]},"Image resource files are normally placed in the res/____________ folder.":{"question":"Image resource files are normally placed in the res/____________ folder.","answer":"drawable","score":"2","options":"input"},"______ is the window flag that will allow the system wallpaper to be shown behind the activity window.":{"question":"______ is the window flag that will allow the system wallpaper to be shown behind the activity window.","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"FLAG_SHOW_DECORATIONS"},{"key":"B.","value":"FLAG_SHOW_WALLPAPER"},{"key":"C.","value":"FLAG_TRANSULUCENT"}]},"To generate simple tweened animations, Android provides the package ___.":{"question":"To generate simple tweened animations, Android provides the package ___.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"android.view.animation"},{"key":"B.","value":"android.animation.view"},{"key":"C.","value":"android.shape"}]},"A/an ______________ object can be updated by background threads very quickly and therefore is ideal for video playback, camera previews, and two-dimensional games.":{"question":"A/an ______________ object can be updated by background threads very quickly and therefore is ideal for video playback, camera previews, and two-dimensional games.","answer":"SurfaceView","score":"2","options":"input"},"What measure of time is used to specify an animation duration in Android?":{"question":"What measure of time is used to specify an animation duration in Android?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Microsecond"},{"key":"B.","value":"Second"},{"key":"C.","value":"Nanosecond"},{"key":"D.","value":"Millisecond"}]},"Common data formats, or audio encoding, supported by Android are ___.":{"question":"Common data formats, or audio encoding, supported by Android are ___.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"AAC, MP3, PCM"},{"key":"B.","value":"AAC, MP3, WAV"},{"key":"C.","value":"MP3, WAV, PCM"}]},"Which of the following is not a parameter of the onFling() callback method?":{"question":"Which of the following is not a parameter of the onFling() callback method?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"The X velocity of the two MotionEvents that started and triggered the callback."},{"key":"B.","value":"The X distance of the two MotionEvents that started and triggered the callback."},{"key":"C.","value":"The MotionEvent that triggered the callback."},{"key":"D.","value":"The MotionEvent that started the fling gesture."}]},"What color would a pixel be if it was set using setPixel(x, y, Color.argb(Color.alpha(p), 100, 100, 100)?":{"question":"What color would a pixel be if it was set using setPixel(x, y, Color.argb(Color.alpha(p), 100, 100, 100)?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"gray"},{"key":"B.","value":"white"},{"key":"C.","value":"black"},{"key":"D.","value":"red"}]},"Positive g-forces indicate what?":{"question":"Positive g-forces indicate what?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"no acceleration"},{"key":"B.","value":"horizontal acceleration"},{"key":"C.","value":"downward acceleration"},{"key":"D.","value":"upward acceleration"}]},"For every ACTION_DOWN motion event, a ____ is called.":{"question":"For every ACTION_DOWN motion event, a ____ is called.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onSingleTapUp()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onLongPress()"},{"key":"C.","value":"onDown()."}]},"Other terms for _______________ are parallelism and concurrency.":{"question":"Other terms for _______________ are parallelism and concurrency.","answer":"multithreading","score":"2","options":"input"},"What function must be called so that a View's canvas is redrawn?":{"question":"What function must be called so that a View's canvas is redrawn?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"redraw()"},{"key":"B.","value":"invalidate()"},{"key":"C.","value":"repaint()"},{"key":"D.","value":"createBitmap()"}]},"The root element of a drawable graphic is _______.":{"question":"The root element of a drawable graphic is _______.","answer":"shape","score":"2","options":"input"},"A ________ is a device component that measures a physical quantity, such as the tilt of a device, a sudden shake, or an increase in pressure, and then converts it into a signal that can be interpreted by an application.":{"question":"A ________ is a device component that measures a physical quantity, such as the tilt of a device, a sudden shake, or an increase in pressure, and then converts it into a signal that can be interpreted by an application.","answer":"sensor","score":"2","options":"input"},"The Canvas method that returns the width of the current drawing layer is ___________.":{"question":"The Canvas method that returns the width of the current drawing layer is ___________.","answer":"getWidth()","score":"2","options":"input"},"A camera-based application is often enhanced by the user of a(n) ______________ sensor.":{"question":"A camera-based application is often enhanced by the user of a(n) ______________ sensor.","answer":"accelerometer","score":"2","options":"input"},"When a touch event occurs, what details are provided by the system?":{"question":"When a touch event occurs, what details are provided by the system?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Location of the finger"},{"key":"B.","value":"Amount of pressure being applied"},{"key":"C.","value":"Size of the finger"},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these"}]},"How can a thread be created?":{"question":"How can a thread be created?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Implement the Runnable interface and Extend the Thread class"},{"key":"B.","value":"Add it to the AndroidManifest.xml"},{"key":"C.","value":"Extend the Thread class"},{"key":"D.","value":"Implement the Runnable interface"}]},"List two motion sensors.":{"question":"List two motion sensors.","answer":"Accelerometer and gyroscope","score":"2","options":"input"},"When would an accelerometer produce the X, Y, Z values of 0, 0, 9.8?":{"question":"When would an accelerometer produce the X, Y, Z values of 0, 0, 9.8?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"When the device is in landscape orientation."},{"key":"B.","value":"When the device is falling straight down with no movement in the x or y direction."},{"key":"C.","value":"When the device is sitting flat on a table pointing north with the screen facing up."},{"key":"D.","value":"When the device is in portrait orientation."}]},"The ________ image file format is the preferred format in Android for displaying images.":{"question":"The ________ image file format is the preferred format in Android for displaying images.","answer":"PNG","score":"2","options":"input"},"Motion events describe movement in terms of":{"question":"Motion events describe movement in terms of","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"An action code."},{"key":"B.","value":"A set of axis values."},{"key":"C.","value":"All of these."}]},"A(n) __________ needs to be invoked to activate the external camera application.":{"question":"A(n) __________ needs to be invoked to activate the external camera application.","answer":"Intent","score":"2","options":"input"},"Android users often experience sensors by means of ___.":{"question":"Android users often experience sensors by means of ___.","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"An accelerometer."},{"key":"B.","value":"A camera."},{"key":"C.","value":"GPS."},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these."}]},"Which of these are not supported by the MediaPlayer?":{"question":"Which of these are not supported by the MediaPlayer?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Playing audio files."},{"key":"B.","value":"Playing video streams over a network."},{"key":"C.","value":"Displaying a visual media controller featuring play/pause, rewind, and other control buttons."},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these are supported by the MediaPlayer."}]},"What method(s) would be used to determine if external storage is available to be read and written to?":{"question":"What method(s) would be used to determine if external storage is available to be read and written to?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"getExternalStorageState() and getExternalStorageDirectory()"},{"key":"B.","value":"isDriveReadandWrite()"},{"key":"C.","value":"getExternalStorageState()"},{"key":"D.","value":"getExternalStorageDirectory()"}]},"The gyroscope measures the rate of rotation around ___.":{"question":"The gyroscope measures the rate of rotation around ___.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Two axes."},{"key":"B.","value":"One axis."},{"key":"C.","value":"Three axes."}]},"What is an object that implements the SurfaceHolder interface used for?":{"question":"What is an object that implements the SurfaceHolder interface used for?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Edits and re-renders the drawing surface."},{"key":"B.","value":"Sends messages to the SurfaceView."},{"key":"C.","value":"Manages the creation of the SurfaceView."},{"key":"D.","value":"Manages the creation of the SurfaceView and sends messages to the SurfaceView."}]},"Most Android devices use ___________ touchscreens which rely on the electrical conductivity produced by the touch of a finger.":{"question":"Most Android devices use ___________ touchscreens which rely on the electrical conductivity produced by the touch of a finger.","answer":"capacitive","score":"2","options":"input"},"Android provides a database software library called ____________ to store information in a database.":{"question":"Android provides a database software library called ____________ to store information in a database.","answer":"SQLite","score":"2","options":"input"},"The ___ callback occurs whenever the user has performed an onDown motion, but has not yet completed any other movement.":{"question":"The ___ callback occurs whenever the user has performed an onDown motion, but has not yet completed any other movement.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onSingleTapUp()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onLongPress()"},{"key":"C.","value":"onShowPress()"}]},"The ________________ class simplifies motion events by identifying the triggered event and delegating calls to a GestureListener.":{"question":"The ________________ class simplifies motion events by identifying the triggered event and delegating calls to a GestureListener.","answer":"GestureDetector","score":"2","options":"input"},"______ is the window flag that will keep the device's screen turned on as along as the activity window is visible to the user.":{"question":"______ is the window flag that will keep the device's screen turned on as along as the activity window is visible to the user.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"FLAG_KEEP_SCREEN"},{"key":"B.","value":"FLAG_SHOW"},{"key":"C.","value":"FLAG_FULLSCREEN"}]},"The ___ can be used to determine if the device is facing up or down.":{"question":"The ___ can be used to determine if the device is facing up or down.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"pitch"},{"key":"B.","value":"roll"},{"key":"C.","value":"yaw"}]},"Why would a programmer choose to use a ScaleGestureDetector?":{"question":"Why would a programmer choose to use a ScaleGestureDetector?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"To determine how many pointers are being used in a multitouch gesture."},{"key":"B.","value":"To determine the scale of the distance between pointers in a multitouch gesture."},{"key":"C.","value":"To determine if a pinch or spread gesture was being used."},{"key":"D.","value":"To determine if a multitouch gesture was being used."}]},"Interaction between an Android thread and the UI thread is accomplished using a _____________________ object.":{"question":"Interaction between an Android thread and the UI thread is accomplished using a _____________________ object.","answer":"UI thread Handler","score":"2","options":"input"},"What is likely to happen when a background thread uses a Handler object (that is created on the UI thread) to update the user interface?":{"question":"What is likely to happen when a background thread uses a Handler object (that is created on the UI thread) to update the user interface?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"ANR"},{"key":"B.","value":"The application will crash."},{"key":"C.","value":"The user interface will update much more slowly."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"What class provides a timing engine for running animations that calculate animated values and set them on target objects?":{"question":"What class provides a timing engine for running animations that calculate animated values and set them on target objects?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Material design"},{"key":"B.","value":"ValueAnimator"},{"key":"C.","value":"AnimatorThread"},{"key":"D.","value":"Circular reveal"}]},"Which of these GestureDectector callback methods does not get called when the user performs a scroll gesture?":{"question":"Which of these GestureDectector callback methods does not get called when the user performs a scroll gesture?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onDown()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onFling()"},{"key":"C.","value":"onScroll()"},{"key":"D.","value":"onShowPress()"}]},"The SensorEventListener interface uses two callback methods: _____________________ and ______________________.":{"question":"The SensorEventListener interface uses two callback methods: _____________________ and ______________________.","answer":"onAccuracyChanged(), onSensorChanged()","score":"2","options":"input"},"The ___________________ class provides a collection of methods to report on the properties of a touch gesture.":{"question":"The ___________________ class provides a collection of methods to report on the properties of a touch gesture.","answer":"MotionEvent class","score":"2","options":"input"},"Sound files are placed in what directory of an Android project?":{"question":"Sound files are placed in what directory of an Android project?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"res/raw"},{"key":"B.","value":"res/audio"},{"key":"C.","value":"res/sound"},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"What is it called when an Android app is no longer responding to the user?":{"question":"What is it called when an Android app is no longer responding to the user?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"multithreaded"},{"key":"B.","value":"crashed"},{"key":"C.","value":"CUI"},{"key":"D.","value":"ANR"}]},"A ___ is the rotation angle around the world-frame x-axis. .":{"question":"A ___ is the rotation angle around the world-frame x-axis. .","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"pitch"},{"key":"B.","value":"yaw"},{"key":"C.","value":"roll"}]},"A/an _____________ provides exclusive access to a resource that is being shared among multiple threads.":{"question":"A/an _____________ provides exclusive access to a resource that is being shared among multiple threads.","answer":"lock","score":"2","options":"input"},"What is the first action type sent to a View's drag event listener when the dragged object's drag shadow first enters the bounding box of a View?":{"question":"What is the first action type sent to a View's drag event listener when the dragged object's drag shadow first enters the bounding box of a View?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"ACTION_DRAG_ENTERED"},{"key":"B.","value":"ACTION_DRAG_ENDED"},{"key":"C.","value":"ACTION_DROP"},{"key":"D.","value":"ACTION_DRAG_LOCATION"}]},"The method ________________ returns a resources instance for an application's package.":{"question":"The method ________________ returns a resources instance for an application's package.","answer":"getResources()","score":"2","options":"input"},"What method is called automatically when a View's canvas needs to be drawn?":{"question":"What method is called automatically when a View's canvas needs to be drawn?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onDraw()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onDisplay()"},{"key":"C.","value":"getPaint()"},{"key":"D.","value":"invalidate()"}]},"When the GestureDetector's onFling() callback is triggered, what other callbacks are triggered?":{"question":"When the GestureDetector's onFling() callback is triggered, what other callbacks are triggered?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onDown()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onShowPress()"},{"key":"C.","value":"onScroll()"},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these"}]},"The method _____________ can be used to obtain the power requirements for a sensor.":{"question":"The method _____________ can be used to obtain the power requirements for a sensor.","answer":"getPower()","score":"2","options":"input"},"When tracking a multitouch gesture, what is the primary pointer?":{"question":"When tracking a multitouch gesture, what is the primary pointer?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"The second finger that touches the screen."},{"key":"B.","value":"The first finger that touches the screen."},{"key":"C.","value":"The first finger that moves."},{"key":"D.","value":"The first finger that stops touching the screen."}]},"The __________ is the main thread of execution for a given Android application.":{"question":"The __________ is the main thread of execution for a given Android application.","answer":"UI thread","score":"2","options":"input"},"For applications that require the retrieval of audio files locaed on a given device, the __________________ class, is used to access these files.":{"question":"For applications that require the retrieval of audio files locaed on a given device, the __________________ class, is used to access these files.","answer":"ContentResolver","score":"2","options":"input"},"What Android class allows units of work to be executed or processed sequentially on a single thread?":{"question":"What Android class allows units of work to be executed or processed sequentially on a single thread?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Runnable"},{"key":"B.","value":"Handler"},{"key":"C.","value":"Looper"},{"key":"D.","value":"Thread"}]},"What arguments get passed to the startDrag() function to start the drag-and-drop process?":{"question":"What arguments get passed to the startDrag() function to start the drag-and-drop process?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"The data to be dragged"},{"key":"B.","value":"The data to be dragged and A DragShadowBuilder"},{"key":"C.","value":"A DragShadowBuilder"},{"key":"D.","value":"The object that will receive the data when dropped"}]},"For every touch gesture that occurs on a touchscreen a(n) __________________ callback will be triggered.":{"question":"For every touch gesture that occurs on a touchscreen a(n) __________________ callback will be triggered.","answer":"onTouchEvent()","score":"2","options":"input"},"The res/anim directory is for storing what type of XML files?":{"question":"The res/anim directory is for storing what type of XML files?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"MediaPlayer animations"},{"key":"B.","value":"Transition animations"},{"key":"C.","value":"Animations featuring recursive drawing"},{"key":"D.","value":"Drawable animations for frame-by-frame animation sequences"}]},"The ___ is called when a long press occurs with the initial onDown MotionEvent that triggered it.":{"question":"The ___ is called when a long press occurs with the initial onDown MotionEvent that triggered it.","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onSingleTapUp()"},{"key":"B.","value":"onLongPress()"},{"key":"C.","value":"onShowPress()"}]},"When the secondary pointer is removed from the screen in a multitouch gesture, what MotionEvent is triggered?":{"question":"When the secondary pointer is removed from the screen in a multitouch gesture, what MotionEvent is triggered?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"ACTION_POINTER_DOWN"},{"key":"B.","value":"ACTION_UP"},{"key":"C.","value":"ACTION_POINTER_UP"},{"key":"D.","value":"ACTION_DOWN"}]},"Why would the SensorManager.getDefaultSensor(type) method return null?":{"question":"Why would the SensorManager.getDefaultSensor(type) method return null?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"The sensor of the given type is currently deactivated."},{"key":"B.","value":"The device has one or more sensors of the given type."},{"key":"C.","value":"The device does not have a sensor of the given type."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"An android device's camera application may request an image capture using ____.":{"question":"An android device's camera application may request an image capture using ____.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Media.getImage"},{"key":"B.","value":"Media.IMAGE_CAPTURE"},{"key":"C.","value":"MediaStore.ACTION_IMAGE_CAPTURE"}]},"____________ provides the resources for handling media playback.":{"question":"____________ provides the resources for handling media playback.","answer":"MediaPlayer","score":"2","options":"input"},"A(n) ____________ is an inertial sensor that provide latency-free measurement of rotations without being affected by external forces, including magnetic and gravitational factors.":{"question":"A(n) ____________ is an inertial sensor that provide latency-free measurement of rotations without being affected by external forces, including magnetic and gravitational factors.","answer":"gyroscopes","score":"2","options":"input"},"What would it mean if the MotionEvent's getPointerCount() method returned the value 2?":{"question":"What would it mean if the MotionEvent's getPointerCount() method returned the value 2?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"There are two motion events that previously been triggered by the touch."},{"key":"B.","value":"There are two fingers currently touching the screen."},{"key":"C.","value":"The x-axis of the tap event is two."},{"key":"D.","value":"A double-tap event was detected."}]},"______ is the window flag that can be used to hide the status bar.":{"question":"______ is the window flag that can be used to hide the status bar.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"FLAG_KEEP_SCREEN"},{"key":"B.","value":"FLAG_HIDE_DECORATIONS"},{"key":"C.","value":"FLAG_FULLSCREEN"}]},"Which of these statements is not true about the UI thread?":{"question":"Which of these statements is not true about the UI thread?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"The UI thread should not perform tasks that take longer than a few seconds."},{"key":"B.","value":"The UI thread should be used to update the user interface."},{"key":"C.","value":"The UI thread can run an Activity."},{"key":"D.","value":"The UI thread cannot run a Service."}]},"A widget called ______________ is a type of AdapterView that displays items in a vertically scrolling list.":{"question":"A widget called ______________ is a type of AdapterView that displays items in a vertically scrolling list.","answer":"ListView","score":"2","options":"input"},"What technology do most Android devices use for their touchscreens?":{"question":"What technology do most Android devices use for their touchscreens?","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Capacitive touchscreens"},{"key":"B.","value":"Infrared light"},{"key":"C.","value":"Resistive touchscreens"},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"What database operation would use a ContentValues object?":{"question":"What database operation would use a ContentValues object?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"SELECT"},{"key":"B.","value":"DELETE"},{"key":"C.","value":"INSERT"},{"key":"D.","value":"SELECT or INSERT"}]},"The method ________________ returns the base context of an application.":{"question":"The method ________________ returns the base context of an application.","answer":"getBaseContext()","score":"2","options":"input"},"When using the VelocityTracker to obtain the X and Y velocities of a fling gesture, what VelocityTracker method must be called immediately before getXVelocity() and getYVelocity()?":{"question":"When using the VelocityTracker to obtain the X and Y velocities of a fling gesture, what VelocityTracker method must be called immediately before getXVelocity() and getYVelocity()?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"clear()"},{"key":"B.","value":"addMovement()"},{"key":"C.","value":"computeCurrentVelocity()"},{"key":"D.","value":"obtain()"}]},"What element in a &lt;shape&gt; Drawable would be used to make the interior of the shape a solid green?":{"question":"What element in a &lt;shape&gt; Drawable would be used to make the interior of the shape a solid green?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"&lt;stroke&gt;"},{"key":"B.","value":"&lt;interior&gt;"},{"key":"C.","value":"&lt;solid&gt;"},{"key":"D.","value":"&lt;gradient&gt;"}]},"What is it called when an application does several things at once?":{"question":"What is it called when an application does several things at once?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"multithreading"},{"key":"B.","value":"parallelism"},{"key":"C.","value":"concurrency"},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these"}]},"What image file type is not supported by Android ImageViews?":{"question":"What image file type is not supported by Android ImageViews?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"JPG"},{"key":"B.","value":"GIF"},{"key":"C.","value":"PNG"},{"key":"D.","value":"BMP"}]},"What type of SQL statement are you likely to use in a SQLiteOpenHelper.onUpgrade() method when a change to the schema requires a table to be re-created?":{"question":"What type of SQL statement are you likely to use in a SQLiteOpenHelper.onUpgrade() method when a change to the schema requires a table to be re-created?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"SELECT"},{"key":"B.","value":"UPGRADE"},{"key":"C.","value":"DROP TABLE"},{"key":"D.","value":"INSERT"}]},"What kind of MotionEvent indicates the start of a multitouch gesture?":{"question":"What kind of MotionEvent indicates the start of a multitouch gesture?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"ACTION_POINTER_DOWN"},{"key":"B.","value":"ACTION_POINTER_UP"},{"key":"C.","value":"ACTION_DOWN"},{"key":"D.","value":"ACTION_MOVE"}]},"If an onTouchEvent() callback registered an ACTION_DOWN with an X value of 10 and an ACTION_UP with an X value of 35, then a fling occurred going in what direction?":{"question":"If an onTouchEvent() callback registered an ACTION_DOWN with an X value of 10 and an ACTION_UP with an X value of 35, then a fling occurred going in what direction?","answer":"D.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Bottom to top"},{"key":"B.","value":"Top to bottom"},{"key":"C.","value":"Left to right"},{"key":"D.","value":"Right to left"}]},"Also called ____, gyroscopes measure how quickly an object rotates.":{"question":"Also called ____, gyroscopes measure how quickly an object rotates.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"Angular rate sensors"},{"key":"B.","value":"Yaw sensors"},{"key":"C.","value":"Pitch sensors"},{"key":"D.","value":"All of these."}]},"Which of the methods below is not a method supplied by the Bitmap class?":{"question":"Which of the methods below is not a method supplied by the Bitmap class?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"extractAlpha()"},{"key":"B.","value":"getRowBytes()"},{"key":"C.","value":"negateImage()"},{"key":"D.","value":"copy()"}]},"What tween animation property is used to ensure that a transformation that was applied will continue to apply after the duration of the transformation has expired?":{"question":"What tween animation property is used to ensure that a transformation that was applied will continue to apply after the duration of the transformation has expired?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"android:fillBefore"},{"key":"B.","value":"android:persist"},{"key":"C.","value":"android:fillAfter"},{"key":"D.","value":"android:startOffset"}]},"Permission for writing to external storage can be set using a &lt;_______________&gt; tag in the AndroidManifest.xml file.":{"question":"Permission for writing to external storage can be set using a &lt;_______________&gt; tag in the AndroidManifest.xml file.","answer":"&lt;uses-permission&gt;","score":"2","options":"input"},"The ____ callback is used for signaling when a particular motion event has occurred.":{"question":"The ____ callback is used for signaling when a particular motion event has occurred.","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"TouchDetector.OnTouchListener."},{"key":"B.","value":"GestureDeector.OnGestureListener"},{"key":"C.","value":"All of these."}]},"What is likely to happen when a background thread tries to update the user interface?":{"question":"What is likely to happen when a background thread tries to update the user interface?","answer":"B.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"ANR"},{"key":"B.","value":"The application will crash."},{"key":"C.","value":"The user interface will update much more slowly."},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"Basic animations are supported by ___.":{"question":"Basic animations are supported by ___.","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"AlphaAnimation"},{"key":"B.","value":"ScaleAnimation"},{"key":"C.","value":"All of these"}]},"When creating a background thread, in what method does a programmer place the time-consuming code?":{"question":"When creating a background thread, in what method does a programmer place the time-consuming code?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"thread()"},{"key":"B.","value":"start()"},{"key":"C.","value":"run()"},{"key":"D.","value":"execute()"}]},"What types of files can be stored in the res/drawable directory?":{"question":"What types of files can be stored in the res/drawable directory?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"PNG"},{"key":"B.","value":"XML"},{"key":"C.","value":"PNG and XML"},{"key":"D.","value":"None of these"}]},"The ____ method is automatically called when a tap occurs with the down MotionEvent that triggered it.":{"question":"The ____ method is automatically called when a tap occurs with the down MotionEvent that triggered it.","answer":"A.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"onDown()."},{"key":"B.","value":"onSingleTapUp()"},{"key":"C.","value":"All of these."}]},"An Activity, Service and Broadcast Receiver all run on the ______________.":{"question":"An Activity, Service and Broadcast Receiver all run on the ______________.","answer":"UI thread","score":"2","options":"input"},"What is the purpose of sensor batching?":{"question":"What is the purpose of sensor batching?","answer":"C.","score":"2","options":[{"key":"A.","value":"To reduce power consumption of apps that continually consume sensor data and to increase the speed with which sensor data can be obtained."},{"key":"B.","value":"To simplify the handling of sensor data in an app."},{"key":"C.","value":"To reduce power consumption of apps that continually consume sensor data."},{"key":"D.","value":"To increase the speed with which sensor data can be obtained."}]}},"length":102}